To wrap up this lesson, I want you
to remember the following key points.
Making predictions is important.
You need to do it based on grammatical
structures and the context of the listening.
Remember not to make mistakes in writing the
plural or singular form of the nouns.
If there are no articles like a or
an or quantifiers like many or some before
the blank, you should mark this asterisk next
to the blank, so that when listening, you
can pay more attention to it.
Secondly, you have to focus on the keywords
in the questions to locate which part the
speaker is talking about.
However, this doesn't mean that you have to
wait until you hear the keywords in the
questions, then you just focus on listening for the
answers.
Thirdly, pay attention to signposting language.
You can encounter some words like actually, in
fact, but, whereas, I mean, unfortunately.
The last thing is to check your answers
after listening to avoid grammatical and spelling mistakes.
You won't lose points if you write incorrect
answers, so never leave your answer sheet blank.
Right, let's study hard guys, and I hope
you will achieve your desired scores.
Goodbye and see you in the next lesson.